can you please take down the garbage once
the garbage is still in the kitchen
I told you I'd do it in a minute
you know what really hurts me about it
not the garbage
but that I always have the feeling
I have to remind you of everything
do you know this feeling write it in the comments
and I just think
I will do it later
you know what
I now understand why this hurt you so much
but for you it was 1 sign that I listen to you
that's exactly what I meant
thank you for understanding me now
many disputes in relationships
do not arise because of the matter itself
but because of the meaning the other sees in it
when someone speaks up to something
it is often not about the task
but therefore
to be seen follow for the next situation tomorrow
you definitely know these